Museums of Washington and Lee University - Record Group 34 WLU.RG.0034
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
Museums of Washington and Lee University - Record Group 34
Date Not Yet Determined
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
Lee Chapel (Washington and Lee University)
Washington and Lee University. Reeves Center
Whitehead, James Walter, Sr.
Dobyns, Lloyd Allen, Jr.
WLU.RG.0034
1 Linear Feet
Scope and Contents
This record group contains archived materials about and created by Washington and Lee University's museums, comprised of Lee Chapel and Museum, the Reeves Collection, and the university's art collection, during the course of its regular business, such as official publications and records of its management.
Art; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward)
- General
  - Teaching With UCAH Website, 2016
    Online Access
    The University Library has captured this website using Archive-It. You can view captures online.
    Scope and Contents
    This website was created by Washington and Lee University faculty as as Associated Colleges of the South grant funded project. It seeks to facilitate the cross-disciplinary use of Washington and Lee's art collection by creating a series of multidisciplinary lesson plans focused on objects in the collection.
- Lee Chapel
  - 17th Century Washington Family Indenture, 1658; Washington, Robert (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Parchment document from Robert Washington and Peter Begin to John Peter.
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    This item (# 280.357.2) is own deposit from Lee Chapel.
    Begin, Peter
  - 17th Century Washington Family Indenture, 1649; Washington, Robert (Box 1, Folder 1)
    parchment document from Robert Washington to Nathaniel Woolinard.
    Ths item (# 280.357.1) is on deposit from Lee Chapel.
    Woolinard, Nathaniel
  - "The Lee Chapel, Some Facts about the Restoration" brochure, Undated; 3 Item
    There are two versions of the brochure.
  - Lee Chapel booklet, Undated; 4 Item
    There are two versions of this booklet, both undated.
  - Lee Chapel and Museum brochure, Undated; 2 Item
  - The Lee Museum brochure, Undated; 1 Item
  - Invitation to Lee Chapel's Rededication Ceremony, 1963-10-11; 1 Item
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Exercises, 1883; Miley, Michael; 2 Item; One copy is hard bound and in poor condition.
    title page reads 'Ceremonies Connected with the Inauguration of the Mausoleum and the Unveiling of the Recumbent Figure of General Robert Edward Lee.' Includes a historical sketch of the Lee Memorial Association by W. Allan, schedule of the inauguration program, and transcriptions of the speeches given including one by John W. Daniel, LL.D. The hard copy also includes several Michael Miley photos.
    Daniels, Jonathan; Lee Memorial Association
  - Let the Organ Play On, Celebrating 142 Years of the Lee Chapel Organ, 2014-11-03
  - Commissioning Ceremony, Lee Chapel, 2013-05-22
    Washington and Lee University. ROTC
  - Lee Chapel Museum Rededication, 1998-10-03
    Washington and Lee University. Lee Chapel
  - Lee Chapel & Museum, Washington and Lee, Flyer
  - Lee Chapel & Museum Shop, Washington and Lee University, Flyer
  - A Guide to Washington and Lee University Museum Collections, Flyer
    Washington and Lee University. Lee Chapel; Washington and Lee University. Reeves Center; Washington and Lee University. Washington Hall; Washington and Lee University. Watson Pavilion
- Reeves Collection
  - James Whitehead Audio-Visual Records, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr.; 9 Item (Audio recordings of Herreshoff reading); 2 Linear Feet (Video recordings)
    Nine betacam recordings from a talk by James Whitehead entitled "Fragile Union" given at the Reeves Center Dedication.
  - L. Dobyns recording, Dobyns, Lloyd Allen, Jr.; 1 Item
    One betacam tape of L. Dobyns speaking about the Reeves Collection.
  - Old George Restored: The Reeves Center Display, 1992; 2 Item
    Separated Materials
    Program from the Reeves Center display about restoration of the Old George statue and a newspaper clipping about the statue.
  - Publications about Reeves materials used in exhibits at other museums, 1974, undated
  - Audiorecordings of "Decorative Arts Trust and Washington and Lee University," China Trade Symposium, 1982-09-09-1982-09-12; Fuchs, Ronald, II; Tinsley, Thomas W.; 15 Cassettes 1-7/8 ips speed, no Dolby, various time
    Gift of Ron Fuchs II.
    These 15 audio cassettes contain the recordings of the talks given on Decorative Arts Trust and Washington and Lee University during the 1982 Chinan Trade Symposium. These talks occurred for the opening of the Reeves Center.
    China trade porcelain; Fuchs, Ronald, II
- Art Collection
  - American Painting at Washington and Lee University: Some Nineteenth-Century Examples, 1976; Washington and Lee University. Art Collection; 1 Item
    Program from an exhibit entitled American Painting at Washington and Lee University: Some Nineteenth-Century Examples, which was held from January 5-22, 1976. The project was sponsored by the National Endowment for the Arts.
    Painting, American
  - The Stan Kamen Collection of Western Art at Washington and Lee, undated; 1 Item
    Brochure about the Stan Kamen Collection of Western Art at Washington and Lee.
    Painting, American; Kamen, Stan
  - Catalogue of the Metropolitan Museum of Art Loan Exhibit, 1950-10-30; 2 Item
  - Preliminary descriptions of paintings owned by Washington and Lee University, Undated
  - The Washington-Custis-Lee Collection of 18th and Early 19th Century Family Portraits exhibit brochure, 1973-10-12; 2 Item
  - Program for Marion Montague Junkin 1905-1977 memorial exhibition, 1979
  - Art Around Campus Videos, 2011; Carlson, Renata; Moryan, Claire; Denniston, Rachel; Davies, John; Serendinski, Andrew; 8 Item
    These videos about pieces of art in Washington and Lee University's Art Collection were created by student interns during the summer of 2011. Students chose pieces that interested them and then researched the works of art.
    View materials from this collection online via W&L's Digital Archive
    College Students; Video recording; Wynn, Evelyn Dawson; Prohaska, Raymond Joseph; Hiroshige, Andō; Watanabe, Sadao; Stella, Frank; Nesbitt, Lowell; McCarthy, Frank C.; Cooper, A. D. M.
- James Whitehead Papers, 1975-1992; WLU-RG-34; Whitehead, James Walter, Sr.; 8 Linear Feet
  This series includes the persona papers of James Whitehead, former director of University Relations, assistant to the president, treasurer, and director of the Reeves Center at Washington and Lee University. These records are from his time as the director of the Reeves Center, and reflect different exhibitions, donor relations, and general correspondence during that time. Much of the collection is correspondence between Whitehead and other museum curators, directors of historical societies, and donors. Includes museum pamphlets, institutional publications, and photographs of collections, and occasionally Whitehead himself. Major subjects of interests covered in the records include matierals concerning the Bicentennial Celebration of American Independence, Foreign Advisory Services (i.e. repossession of Reeves Collection), the Reeves Center, the Morris House, Skylark, Wamsutta Hills, exhibitions of Louise Herreshoff's work, the Reeves Collection of fine China, and miscellaneous correspondence. Also includes some files from Tom Litzenberg, the successor for Whitehead's role as director of the Reeves' center.
  Arrangement
  The bulk of this series is arranged alphabetically, using last names when referring to a specific person. Toward the end of the collection, especially in miscellaneous correspondence, the papers are organized chronologically.
  Related Materials
  Researchers might also use the Louise Herreshoff Papers for detailed correspondence and primary source records documenting her personal life, as well as those of her husband, Euchlin Reeves. Some of Whitehead's records and work on his biography of Louise Herreshoff, "A Fragile Union," are included in this collection. Washington and Lee University Record Group 34 also includes audio recordings of a presentation made by Whitehead on "A Fragile Union."
  Art museums; Washington and Lee University; China trade porcelain -- Collectors and collecting; China trade porcelain; Art, American; Washington and Lee University. Reeves Center; Herreshoff, Louise; Reeves, Euchlin
  - Box 1: A through Cha (Box 1)
    This is the first box of the James Whitehead Papers, and includes materials related to the Bicentennial in 1976, as well as correspondence with people and organizations between letters "A" through "Cha."
    - Alvin D. Aisenberg, D.D.S. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - American Art by David Meschutt (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - American Association of Museums (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - American Association for State and Local History (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - American China Trade Museum (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Stephenson Boone Andrews - Class of '81 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Antique Monthly (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Antiques (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Antiques (correspondence, pamphlets, etc.) (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Applicants (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Appraisers (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Archeological Society of Virginia (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Anne Tobin Armstrong - Armstrong Ranch, Texas, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Articles: Reeves Center exhibitions and publications, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Washington and Lee University. Reeves Center
    - Athenian Society (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Atlanta, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - James Avarti (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - James M. Ballengee (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Dr. Herman Barlow and Mrs. Herman Barlow (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Mr. C. Waller Barrett (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - James B. Bell - Director of New York Historical Society (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Stuart Bell Jr. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Adrian and Richard Bendheim (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Dr. and Mrs. Irwin R. Berman (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Bicentennial, 1976; Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Bicentennial (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Alfred E. Bissell, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Daniel Blain Jr. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Boar's Head Inn (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Gerald Boehm (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Dr. and Mrs. Leonard C. Borland (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Boston, Massachusetts (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Patrick T. Brennan, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Irving Bricken (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Thomas H. Broadus Jr. (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Dr. Katherine L. Brown - Executive Director of Woodrow Wilson Birthplace (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Michael Burke (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Carter L. Burgess (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Burlington Industries (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Business Meetings, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Carpets / Rugs (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - H. Jackson Cary III (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Pete W. Cawthorn Jr. (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - CHALFA (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Benjamin Chapman - Program Coordinator of the Reeves Center (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Charlottesville Book Club (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Charlottesville Reeves Center Brunch (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Box 2: Che through Lu (Box 2)
    This box contains correspondence and related files between letters "Che" through "Lu." Also contains files related to Foreign Advisory Services.
    - Leslie Cheek (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Frazier Cheston (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Chicago Art Institute, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 2, Folder 51)
      Illinois -- Chicago
    - Chinese Eastern Art and Furniture Company, C/O Lee and Jong (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - A.B. Claytor (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Maurice Cline (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Col Alto (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Columbia, South Carolina - Columbia Museum of Art (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Clement Conger - Curator of White House and State Department (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Alistair Cooke (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Parents of Allen Raymond Cross III (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Julia B. Curtis (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Dan River, Incorporated Home Fashions Division (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Justin W. Dar (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Carl C. Dauterman (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - DAT - Salem Booster (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Prospective Donors (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - East side house settlement (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Goetz B. Eaton (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Raymond Edelmam - Vice President at EF Hutton and Company (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Edison Illuminating Company (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - John Ellis (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - William D. Epps (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - E. Stewart Epley - Memo (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Katherine G. Farnham, Adjunct Curator for Dec. Arts - the High Museum of Arts (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - James Farquhar III, Jr., and Sr. (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Film Companies Related (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Foreign Advisory Service (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Foreign Advisory Service (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Foreign Advisory Service (invoice for purchase), Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Frick Art - Reference Librarian (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Godfrey Edmund Fitzhugh - Skylark Visit (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - William Fine - Hearst Publishing Company - New York City (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Embassy of Federal Republic of Germany (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - German Department (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Governor's Mansion Foundation (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Elizabeth C. Ham (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Mr. and Mrs. George W. Herndon (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - William Howard Herndon (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Robert M. Hicklin Jr., Southern Decorative and Fine Arts (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Mrs. Phillip R. Hirsh, Meadow Lane Lodge (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Historic Lexington Foundation (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Henry Clay Hofheimer II (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Commencement - Honorary Degree Plans (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Joseph Harrell (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Professor Charles Hsiao - Chunge Hwei Industrial Company Ltd., Taipei Thailand (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Insurance at Washington and Lee University (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Dr. Sidney Isenberg (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Jefferson Awards (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - John Bovvier Johnson (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Justice Herbert, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Mrs. Harry M. Kechijian (Belleck Porcelain) (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Robert Keefe, McKinsey and Company Incorporated (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - King's Chandelier Company (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - J.J. Korman and Sons Incorporated (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Krasnow - Washington D.C. (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Lady Cox (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Robert E. Lee IV (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Letters - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Bernard and S. Dean Levy, Incorporated (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Stanley Preston Lewis (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Liberty Hall Dig - Whitehead, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Box 3: Lu through Reeves Center (Box 3)
    - Mrs. George M. Lupton, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Carlyle and Jane Lynch (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Harry Lyons (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Tim McCune, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Brooks McCormick - "The Hope of McCormick Collection of Staffordshire Pottery Selection" (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Coleman C. McGehee (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - John McQuiggan - Producer (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Mrs. Laura P. McCartney (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - M/M. Howard Melton (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Memphis Trip - Whitehead (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Ronn W. Mercer (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Honor Moore (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Missing Items (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Morris House and Skylark (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Morris House - Furnishings Upgrade, 2002-2003; Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - University Museum Materials (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Morris House (1/4) (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Morris House (2/4) (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Morris House (3/4) (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Morris House (4/4) (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Mosbacher Family (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Dr. Arthur Mourot (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Jean McClure Mudge (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Museum of American History (Smithsonian Institution - Ms. Alice Malone) (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - National Museum - Shipei (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Elizabeth Navarro (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - New York City, 1987-01-24-1987-01-27 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - New York Historical Society (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Milburn K. Noell, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - North Carolina - Spring Trip, 1989-03-10-1989-03-12 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Oakencroft Vineyard and Winery - Charlottesville, VA (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Paintings (Miscellaneous) (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Parents' Weekend (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Mr. and Mrs. George Parsons (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - M.W. Paxton, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Ruth and Charles Howard Parmly, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Pennsburg Manor (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Porcelain / Articles (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Porcelain - Chinese (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Porcelain - Presidential (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Porcelain Restoration (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Portugal, Lisbon - Trip (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Portsmouth Museums (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - President's Home (Washington and Lee University) - Display of Reeves Items, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - William W. Pusey (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Reed and Barton Reproduction Photos (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Reed and Barton Reproductions (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Reeves Center Classes - Alumni College, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - The Reeves Center Dinner, 1985-08-07 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Reeves Center - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Alphabetized), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Reeves Center Dinners - Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Box 4: Reeves Students through Washington Trip (Box 4)
    - Reeves Center (Students: Past/present) (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Reeves Center - Student Christmas Dinners, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Reeves Center Visiting Tours Past (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Reeves Center Tour Dates and Shows: Schedules and Porcelain, 1972-1981; Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Reeves Center - Winter Tour, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Washington and Lee University - Reeves Center (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Hazard Reeves (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Restoration (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Rikkyo University - Newsletter (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - George Stanley Robinson (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Winifred N. Hansel: Rockbridge Historical Society (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - The Roving Classroom International (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - Ruder and Finn - Fine Arts (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - San Diego - Gaslamp Quarter Foundation (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Sayers of St. Louis - Mr. Don Jansen (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - The Scotts Irish Society of Virginia (deposit slips, checkbook, etc.) (Box 4, Folder 179)
    - Dr. David Sensabaugh (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Theodore A. Seder (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Sewickeley Valley Hospital - School of Nursing, Mrs. Fred Sharp - Antiques Show (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - John M. Shank (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - Margaret M. Shanks - Pine Valley (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - James B. Sharp - Sharp and Sharp (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Ambassador James C.H. Shen (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - General Wang Sheng of Taiwan (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Skylark (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Skylark (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Stephen Sloan (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Bev Smith (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Smithsonian (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Time-Life Books, Incorporated (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - Tucker Collection - Baccarat and Lalique Crystal (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - John G. Tucker (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - Tuttle Gallery - William C. Mules, Headmaster McDonogh School (Box 4, Box 196)
    - United States Historical Society (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Donald Vaughan (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Virginia Bankers' Associations - Mrs. Barbara A. Garrett (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Virginia Collectors' Guild (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - Treasurer - Search (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Dave Wallace (Graphic Copies) (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Wamsutta (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Wamsutta Hills (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - Wamsutta Hills (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Rockbridge Historical Society (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - Winterthur Guild (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - Ernest Woodward II, Esq. (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - James H. Woosley (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Yorktown (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - Your Own Bin - Storage (Box 4, Folder 211)
    - Jim Yao - Popular Oriental Furniture and Porcelain Mfg. and Co. (Box 4, Folder 212)
    - Charles H. Zeanah (Box 4, Folder 213)
    - Washington Trip, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 214)
  - Box 5: George Washington through Louise Herreshoff (Box 5)
    - Receipt for: George Washington Letter to Board of Trustees (Liberty Hall Academy), Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Westward Ho, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - George A. Whiting (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - W.H. Whitehall, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Williamsburg, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Anne Booth Willis and James H. Willis (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - Richard Alan Winstead (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Whitehall Shop (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Arts - Business Committee for the Arts, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - High Museum of Art (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Saint Louis Art Museum - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Stratford Hall - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Matthew and Elizabeth Sharpe (Spring Mill Antique Shop) (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Yale University Art Gallery, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - Hirschl and Alder Galleries, Incorporated, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - The Society of the Lees of Virginia (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - Childs Gallery, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Santa Barbara Museum of Art, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Kenmore Association, Incorporated - W. Vernon Edenfield, 1980-1990 (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Mary's Gallery - Mr. Pendleton Hogan, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Whitehead Correspondence, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Rockbridge Chapter of the Virginia Museum, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Hirschl and Alder Galleries, Incorporated - Loan Exhibition Spring, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Whitehead Correspondence - Poplar Forest Fund (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Whitehead Correspondence, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Tyron Palace - Donald R. Taylor (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Whitehead Correspondence, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Whitehead Correspondence, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - Los Angeles County Museum, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - Alleghany Highland Arts and Crafts (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Whitehead Correspondence, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - National Museum of Women's Art - Jeanne Hodges - Director (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - National Museum - Washington (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - Visitor Center, 1987-1991 (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - Peabody Museum Salem, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - Sweet Briar Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - Whitehead Correspondence, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - Sweet Briar College (Box 5, Folder 254)